[
  {
    "question": "What is the capital city of California?",
    "choice1": "Los Angeles",
    "choice2": "San Francisco",
    "choice3": "Sacramento",
    "choice4": "San Jose",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was the 2nd President of the United States?",
    "choice1": "John Adams",
    "choice2": "Thomas Jefferson",
    "choice3": "Abraham Lincoln",
    "choice4": "James Madison",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Alexander Graham Bell invented the _____.",
    "choice1": "microwave",
    "choice2": "x-ray machine",
    "choice3": "light bulb",
    "choice4": "telephone",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the only US President to have never been elected to office?",
    "choice1": "Richard Nixon",
    "choice2": "Gerald Ford",
    "choice3": "Lyndon B. Johnson",
    "choice4": "John F. Kennedy",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Which US state was the first to allow women to vote?",
    "choice1": "Arizona",
    "choice2": "Texas",
    "choice3": "Wyoming",
    "choice4": "New York",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Which US state was the first to obtain statehood?",
    "choice1": "Delaware",
    "choice2": "Pennsylvania",
    "choice3": "New York",
    "choice4": "Massachusetts",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these is NOT a member of the Ivy League?",
    "choice1": "Dartmouth College",
    "choice2": "University of Pennsylvania",
    "choice3": "Stanford University",
    "choice4": "Cornell University",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "As of the 2016 election, how many people have served as President of the United States?",
    "choice1": "45",
    "choice2": "50",
    "choice3": "40",
    "choice4": "44",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is NOT based in Seattle, WA?",
    "choice1": "Starbucks Coffee",
    "choice2": "Boeing",
    "choice3": "Amazon",
    "choice4": "Alaska Airlines",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "The top-3 most commonly spoken languages in the US are: English, Spanish, and Chinese. What is the 4th?",
    "choice1": "Tagalog",
    "choice2": "Arabic",
    "choice3": "German",
    "choice4": "Japanese",
    "answer": 1
  }
]